



Junior Full Stack Developer

As a Full Stack Web Developer with digital marketing background, I am seeking an entry-level position in a Tech Company. I am a Brazilian currently residing in Lisbon for 2 years with a valid working permit and am looking to shift my career. My background provides valuable soft skills and my web dev studies provide the hard skills needed for this new path.

KEY SKILLS

NodeJS Javascript React **Photoshop InDesign** Express **HTML & CSS RESTFul APIs Typescript** MongoDB Illustrator Wordpress

TECH PROJECTS ⊘

Dino Era Game Nomadic Ohalo Store WannaGo App

HTML | CSS | JavaScript ExpressJS | NodeJS | MongoGB React | MongoDB | NodeJS TypeScript | JSON | Bootstrap

JavaScript | API

EDUCATION

OUT 2022 - DEZ 2022 AUG 2021 - JULY 2023 AUG 2009 - AUG 2014

Master in New Media and Web Practices **Bachelor of Arts in Communications** Web Development Bootcamp Ironhack Lisbon Nova University Lisbon FACHA - Rio de Janeiro, BR

WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2021 - FEB 2022 Social Media Manager - Papori Interactive Marketing Lisbon, PT

- Marketing and social media strategy for six different accounts;
- Community management across multiple social media channels;
- Reports and data analysis.

JUL 2020 - JUL 2021 Digital Content Specialist - Prado Imóveis Litoral Remote

- Responsible for the company's visual identity and rebranding;
- Digital strategy and content for Facebook and Instagram;
- Social analysis and reports with a focus on engaging the audience and increasing brand awareness. (ROI Estimate, SEO & SMO).

Marketing Coordinator - Woohoo Channel **DEC 2011 - JAN 2019** Rio de Janeiro, BR

- Social media management resulting in an increase of 2M followers. development of relevance and credibility with the audience (Facebook Ads, Google Ads, and WordPress);
- Reports and content performance and recommending strategy changes based on data;
- Coordination on multiple projects simultaneously, ensuring good communication and work-flow between multiple engagement teams;

Contacts You can find me at 🔗 Languages

E-mail: babs.agra@gmail.com LinkedIn Portuguese | Native Phone: +351 912592474 **Github** English | Advanced C1